Look, I'm a lonely guy;
I watch a lot of movies.
(Raj:)Look, Penny,
(Raj:)if you truly want to be romantic,
it needs to come from you.
(Penny:)I get that, but why is this so hard?
(Raj:)Well, you've probably never had
to do this stuff 'cause you're young
(Raj:)and beautiful and men have
always thrown themselves at you.
(Penny:)Yeah, I'm trying to be sad
about that. I can't.
(Sheldon:)Let's see, what's next?
Okay! Here.
(Sheldon:)This is the Magic Marker
(Sheldon:)I was using
when I made the discovery.
(Amy:)I don't think the Smithsonian's
gonna want your marker.
(Sheldon:)And that's why you're not
on the list for my tree fort.
Ooh! Guess who's getting an article
(Sheldon:)written about him in Physics Today?
(Sheldon:)I'll give you a hint.
(Sheldon:)You measured the diameter
of his suspicious mole yesterday.
(Amy:)Sheldon, I'm so proud of you.
(Sheldon:)Well, you should be. My discovery
is spreading like wildfire.